<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Frank&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://gellardo.github.io/blog/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Frank&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Jun 2021 16:07:25 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://gellardo.github.io/blog/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Self-Documenting Makefile</title>
      <link>https://gellardo.github.io/blog/posts/2021-06-10-self-documenting-makefile/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jun 2021 16:07:25 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gellardo.github.io/blog/posts/2021-06-10-self-documenting-makefile/</guid>
      <description>A short one i really liked and I want to document for future-me: Self-documenting Makefiles. Just add a new help target and now you can comment all targets by using ## &amp;lt;comment&amp;gt; after the prerequisites.
The displayed help is generated on the fly so just keep the documentation updated right next to the scripting and enjoy a nicely formatted help for all the important make-targets.
clean: ## clean up leftover files 	@echo &amp;#39;removing files&amp;#39; # will not be included in the help output internal: some-file @echo &amp;#39;doing some internal, not to be called manually things&amp;#39; .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Playing With Rust and Wasm</title>
      <link>https://gellardo.github.io/blog/posts/2020-07-02-playing-with-rust-and-wasm/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 21:52:04 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gellardo.github.io/blog/posts/2020-07-02-playing-with-rust-and-wasm/</guid>
      <description>I have read a lot about how Wasm is great for porting non-JS languages into the browser and maybe even into a general Lambda runtime. Also better security and ability to compile libraries into Wasm and use them in other languages. So I wanted to try it and document my experience using Rust+Wasm to build Game of Life using Wasm.
TLDR: If you want to learn a lot more than I can cover here, read the official rust+wasm introduction instead of watching me stumbling around here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Hugo to run</title>
      <link>https://gellardo.github.io/blog/posts/2020-05-31-getting-hugo-to-run/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 May 2020 22:48:32 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gellardo.github.io/blog/posts/2020-05-31-getting-hugo-to-run/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I wanted to have a really low friction way of practicing technical writing.
As my current employer mostly uses Blogs as PR, my first idea was to try blogging, but to start small without anyone seeing it.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>